Every time a new AI model comes out, it
feels like it tops all the coding
benchmarks. Well, I've spent the better
part of a year evaluating LLMs and their
coding ability. I've built my own custom
suite of evaluation tools. In fact, I'm
working on version three of that. Along
the way, I've learned so much about what
differentiates an LLM and its harnesses.
[music] I'm Adam Larson. You may know me
online as go coder on YouTube or I'm
also the CTO and co-founder of a company
called Railon where we're building very
heavily with AI. I want to take you
through the current state of benchmarks
in eval talk about the places we need to
improve the weaknesses of the current
systems and along the way come away with
a better understanding of AI assisted
coding. I'd love to see you at DevCon
where I'll be speaking on this
particular topic. Register now at
av.io/devcon.
Again, that's a native.io/devcon.
I hope to see you guys there. Take care.